<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<story title="Epic Tale">
  <paragraphs>
    <paragraph>I have left some Christmas gifts for you to find.</paragraph>
    <paragraph>You have found all of your Christmas gifts! I wish you a merry Christmas, and to you a good night.</paragraph>
  </paragraphs>
  <phrases>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is the spirit of giving without a thought of getting. It is happiness because we see joy in people. It is forgetting self and finding time for others. It is discarding the meaningless and stressing the true values. -- Thomas S. Monson
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas isn't a season. It's a feeling. -- Edna Ferber
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas waves a magic wand over this world, and behold, everything is softer and more beautiful. -- Norman Vincent Peale
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      He who has not Christmas in his heart will never find it under a tree. -- Roy L. Smith
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is a season not only of rejoicing but of reflection. -- Winston Churchill
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas gives us the opportunity to pause and reflect on the important things around us - a time when we can look back on the year that has passed and prepare for the year ahead. -- David Cameron
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Maybe Christmas, the Grinch thought, doesn't come from a store. -- Dr. Seuss
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is not a time nor a season, but a state of mind. To cherish peace and goodwill, to be plenteous in mercy, is to have the real spirit of Christmas. -- Calvin Coolidge
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is the day that holds all time together. -- Alexander Smith
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      The spirit of Christmas is the spirit of love and of generosity and of goodness. It illuminates the picture window of the soul, and we look out upon the world's busy life and become more interested in people than in things. -- Thomas S. Monson
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Don't let the past steal your present. This is the message of Christmas: We are never alone. -- Taylor Caldwell
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas... is not an external event at all, but a piece of one's home that one carries in one's heart. -- Freya Stark
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas, my child, is love in action. Every time we love, every time we give, it's Christmas. -- Dale Evans
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      I will honor Christmas in my heart, and try to keep it all the year. -- Charles Dickens
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Happy, happy Christmas, that can win us back to the delusions of our childhood days, recall to the old man the pleasures of his youth, and transport the traveler back to his own fireside and quiet home! -- Charles Dickens
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Every gift which is given, even though is be small, is in reality great, if it is given with affection. -- Pindar
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      At Christmas play and make good cheer, for Christmas comes but once a year. -- Thomas Tusser
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is joy, religious joy, an inner joy of light and peace. -- Pope Francis
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is a tonic for our souls. It moves us to think of others rather than of ourselves. It directs our thoughts to giving. -- B. C. Forbes
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      The excellence of a gift lies in its appropriateness rather than in its value. -- Charles Dudley Warner
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is a season for kindling the fire for hospitality in the hall, the genial flame of charity in the heart. -- Washington Irving
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas and the holidays are the season of giving. It's a time when people are more kind and open-hearted. -- Gisele Bundchen
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Expectancy is the atmosphere for miracles. -- Edwin Louis Cole
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      As we give presents at Christmas, we need to recognize that sharing our time and ourselves is such an important part of giving. -- Gordon B. Hinckley
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is doing a little something extra for someone. -- Charles M. Schulz
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      It is a fine seasoning for joy to think of those we love. -- Moliere
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      A good conscience is a continual Christmas. -- Benjamin Franklin
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas, children, is not a date. It is a state of mind. -- Mary Ellen Chase
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      When you give up yourself, that's when you will feel the true spirit of Christmas. And that's giving that's serving others and that's when you feel fulfilled. -- Joel Osteen
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas is, of course, the time to be home - in heart as well as body. -- Garry Moore
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      The earth has grown old with its burden of care, but at Christmas it always is young, the heart of the jewel burns lustrous and fair, and its soul full of music breaks the air, when the song of angels is sung. -- Phillips Brooks
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      T'was the night before Christmas, when all through the house, not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse. -- Clement Clarke Moore
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas time! That man must be a misanthrope indeed, in whose breast something like a jovial feeling is not roused - in whose mind some pleasant associations are not awakened - by the recurrence of Christmas. -- Charles Dickens
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      My brothers and sisters, may the spirit of love which comes at Christmastime fill our homes and our lives and linger there long after the tree is down and the lights are put away for another year. -- Thomas S. Monson
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas always rustled. It rustled every time, mysteriously, with silver and gold paper, tissue paper and a rich abundance of shiny paper, decorating and hiding everything and giving a feeling of reckless extravagance. -- Tove Jansson
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Now, the essence, the very spirit of Christmas is that we first make believe a thing is so, and lo, it presently turns out to be so. -- Stephen Leacock
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      As dry leaves that before the wild hurricane fly, when they meet with an obstacle, mount to the sky. So up to the house-top the coursers they flew, with the sleigh full of toys, and St. Nicholas too. -- Clement Clarke Moore
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      Christmas renews our youth by stirring our wonder. The capacity for wonder has been called our most pregnant human faculty, for in it are born our art, our science, our religion. -- Ralph W. Sockman
    </phrase>
    <phrase>
      The fact is, we need markers in life, whether we subscribe to a religion or not. And the major holidays, such as Christmas, serve to remind us of the turning world. -- Jay Parini
    </phrase>
  </phrases>
</story>









